
Welcome to Gradle 8.11.1!

Here are the highlights of this release:
 - Parallel load and store for Configuration Cache
 - Java compilation errors at the end of the build output
 - Consolidated report for warnings and deprecations

For more details see https://docs.gradle.org/8.11.1/release-notes.html

Starting a Gradle Daemon, 1 incompatible Daemon could not be reused, use --status for details

> Configure project :app
WARNING: Using flatDir should be avoided because it doesn't support any meta-data formats.

> Configure project :capacitor-cordova-android-plugins
WARNING: Using flatDir should be avoided because it doesn't support any meta-data formats.
